Was that it, grade 1 sorcerer?
You did well running around,
but you're at your limit, aren't you?
Unfortunately...
What?
His cursed energy's increasing?
I'm going into overtime now.
Overtime?
A time-based pact!
He was limiting his own cursed
energy this whole time?!
Fun!
My cursed technique draws
a line along the target and,
using a ratio of 7:3,
creates a weak point at that location.
I can create this line along more than
just their full height or wingspan.
I can designate it along various parts, such
as the head, upper arm, forearm, and so on.
This cursed technique can affect more
than just living creatures, as well.
He's revealing his technique?
You're serious, huh?
At present, the first way I can
see to exorcise this cursed spirit
Playing tag again?
is to continue damaging him until
he runs out of cursed energy.
However, that's not very realistic for me.
The second way is to reduce him
to smithereens with a single blow.
Ratio Technique: Collapse!
What power!
No, more importantly,
cursed energy raced through it?
No way!
It's an expanded technique that imbues
the destroyed target with cursed energy!
It's a wide-range attack
that puts him at risk, too.
So I guess...
I should dodge this one.
I'm retreating for now.
You should get that leg healed quickly.
If we both manage to survive, let's meet again.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Episode 11:  Narrow-minded
Huh?
Did the ground just shake?
Yeah, it did. Intensity 2 or so?
Nope, Ijichi-san's not answering.
Should I really be the one to ask this?
Is it really okay to just ask him
straight-up about that, though?
How much am I allowed to reveal
about Jujutsu Tech, anyway?
Ijichi Kiyotaka
The number you have dialed
cannot be reached at this time.
Just answer!
Wait!
I wonder what's going on.
A button with a swirl?
Yup.
If you meet a student wearing this button
with a swirl, you should be friendly to them.
Because they're jujutsu sorcerers.
I'm sure you'll get along with them.
But the jujutsu sorcerers are
Mahito-san's enemies, right?
Forget it! I'm just going to ask!
Listen, there were people who died at
the theater you went to the other day.
Did you happen to see anything?
A creepy thing like this, maybe?
No, I didn't.
I've only recently started
seeing those clearly.
I see.
Well, I've got nothing else to ask, then!
Huh? That's it?
But could you still wait until my...
I guess he's like my boss... shows up?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks!
Hey.
What were you watching at that theater?
It was a repeat screening of an old movie.
I doubt you'd know it if I told you.
Come on, just tell me.
Human Earthworm
Human Earthworm 3.
That one was super boring!
I got hit so many times over that.
You got hit?
Honestly, it was.
But it's just a splatter film,
so maybe it's our own fault for
asking it to deliver more than that.
But 2 was—
But 2 was pretty good, right?
Yeah! Yeah, it was!
It was the only one with
a way you could enjoy it!
Huh? A way to enjoy it?
Bingo.
Have you seen the entire series?
At first, 2 looks like it wouldn't
be any different from 1 or 3,
but it actually captures
the changing emotions of the perfectionist
who abandons everything.
Mama...
Ah, so that's why I was able to watch 2.
Why?
At first, I couldn't understand
what was good about it,
so I made myself watch it three times.
It had the most effective gory scenes,
too, so it wasn't easy to rewatch.
Why'd you go that far?
Do you like movies, Itadori-kun?
I've been watching a lot of them
lately, for certain reasons.
Though I haven't been seeing them in theaters.
What?
But the emotional impact of finding
a good one at the theater is huge.
Even if on-demand is more convenient.
When was the last time I saw one in a theater?
Take me with you next time
there's one you're into.
Huh?
Oh, need my contact info?
Here.
How do I add friends again?
Oh, Junpei?
Mom.
It's unusual to see you out here.
Is this a friend?
We just met, actually.
We may have just met,
but I think we can be friends.
Really? I hope you get along well, then.
Mom!
I asked you...
to quit smoking.
Oh, right, sorry.
I did promise not to smoke
in front of you anymore.
What's your friend's name?
Itadori Yuuji.
The green onion doesn't suit your look.
Oh, you can tell?
I'm trying to be a woman who doesn't
look good with green onions.
What are you even talking about?
So, Yuuji-kun, care to join us for dinner?
H-Hey! You're just bothering him.
Huh? Are you saying my cooking is a nuisance?
Cramp
Anything you don't like? Any allergies?
Nope!
That sorcerer's more reckless than he looks!
You two went at it quite hard.
Getou!
That guy was interesting.
I learned a lot from him.
Oh?
Even if I'm pulverized, I won't die as
long as I maintain the shape of my soul.
Consumption of cursed energy counts
toward supplementation of the self.
Also, it looks like there's no risk to me,
no matter how much I tweak
the shape of my own soul.
Next time, I'll let loose and
try all kinds of things.
Getou, get me some clothes.
Nope.
What happened to the guy you fought?
I don't know.
He said he was retreating, but he
might be buried under the rubble.
What? You're at Yoshino Junpei's home?!
That's a bit of a...
Oh, it's fine.
Well, I'm about to have dinner.
Dinner?!
I'll head there at once.
If you sense anything odd,
please run immediately.
Even if Yoshino Junpei is involved
in this incident as a perpetrator,
I doubt he could quickly kill
Itadori-kun as he is now.
But still, this is a huge blunder
on my part as his supervisor.
As blithe as Gojou-san is, he might not mind,
but if the adult-of-adults,
Nanami-san, chews me out...
I'll probably cry!
Hurry up now!
You don't want to cry in front
of others at your age, do you?!
Nanami Kento
He's calling me earlier than scheduled!
Yeah, he's going to chew me out!
Hello, I'm sorry.
I just sent you my location data.
Please come and pick me up.
I'm going back to Jujutsu Tech to
receive treatment from Ieiri-san.
Treatment?
Don't worry.
It's not an injury that'll kill me.
That's good.
I'll join up with Itadori-kun soon,
then I'll head your way.
He's not with you?
I'm such an idiot!
I've practiced a lot...
You'll make the best test subject.
Luck's really on my side.
That cursed spirit is a child.
It probably hasn't been very
long since he sprang into being.
He's greedily enjoying his own growth.
The special-grade cursed spirits that Gojou-san
fought had mastered domain expansion.
If he managed to survive, it won't be much
longer before he reaches that stage, too.
On top of that, his victim count
far exceeded our expectations.
Help... me!
We need to exorcise him as soon as possible,
before it's too late.
And then?
So then Takashi-kun says, full of confidence...
This is the larva of an invasive species!
It might be poisonous!
Nobody touch it!
So then I tried picking it up,
and it turned out to be a
konjac noodle from lunch!
Wait, konjac? It was a konjac noodle?!
Mom, you've had too much to drink.
You're funny, Yuuji-kun.
Here, do something funny with these!
She's the worst kind of drunk.
Wilson! Wilson!
Forgive me, Wilson!
That's from Cast Away, isn't it?
You got it!
I don't get it. Is that a movie reference?
Fire!
Your mom's really nice.
Yeah.
School?
It's okay. You don't have to go.
Huh?
Kids your age tend to take
everything too seriously.
School is just a tiny aquarium.
There's a whole ocean out there,
and other aquariums, too.
Pick the one you want.
Hey, that was a really cool
thing to say, wasn't it?
What a brilliant saying. Way to go, me!
What's your mom like?
Uh, I've never met her.
Though I have a few faint
memories of my father...
But my grandpa was there for me.
Oh, sorry. Got a call.
Hello, Ijichi-san?
Yeah, I'm fine.
But we're about to watch a movie.
Okay.
Two hours from now, then.
Two ho—
You're a jujutsu sorcerer, right?
Yeah.
Should I have said that?
Have you... ever killed someone?
No.
But someday you'll have to fight
bad jujutsu sorcerers, right?
What will you do then?
I still wouldn't want to kill them.
Why not? They're bad people.
It's like... I just think, if I killed anyone,
the option of "killing" would
force its way into my life.
The value of life would become ambiguous...
I wouldn't even understand the importance
of those I care about anymore.
And that scares me.
People don't have hearts.
That idea saved me.
It gave me strength.
But if killing someone
would mean tainting my soul...
then I can't kill anyone.
Darn, I feel asleep.
Did Yuuji-kun go home already?
Gah! It's already this late?
I need to clean up.
What's this?
A finger?
JUJUTSU KAISEN
After the Satozakura High School Incident
After the incident at Satozakura High School,
we discovered the corpse of Yoshino Nagi,
Yoshino Junpei's mother, at their home,
along with an unsealed Sukuna's Finger—
his second left arm's pinky finger.
We believe Yoshino Nagi was attacked by
cursed spirits drawn to Sukuna's Finger.
Her remains were missing
everything from the waist down.
There were no visible or detectable
traces of blood found on-site,
and Yoshino Nagi's body was
lying down in her bedroom.
Lifting up the blanket revealed only cold
packs and ice bags spread out beneath it.
Are you saying I'd get in the way, Nanamin?
You're injured, aren't you?
Next time, take me with you.
"My partner died.
But I wasn't there at the time.
Why? Because I'm a child."
You're a strong kid, so help others.
I don't want any of that.
You can't.
As you already know, this patchwork
cursed spirit uses transfigured people.
There are some people who are beyond saving.
If you continue this work,
there will a come a time when you're
forced to kill a person yourself.
But this is not that time.
I still wouldn't want to kill them.
And that scares me.
Please understand this.
Being a child is not a sin.
I would like to ask you to continue
monitoring Yoshino Junpei.
I didn't own any black clothing,
so I opened my mom's closet
and put on the first
thing that caught my eye.
The smell of the morning air and the
commute to school were all familiar,
but today...
This is
a cursed object known as "Sukuna"
that attracts other curses.
What was a thing like that doing in my home?!
There are many curse users who
earn money by cursing people.
It was probably done by one of them.
With money and connections,
it's easy to curse someone to death.
Can you think of anyone?
Anyone who might hold a grudge
against you or your mother?
Or perhaps...
someone dark and gloomy,
with plenty of money and free time?
The certificate of commendation
and the prize for the finest work in the
national book report competition goes to
Itou Shouta.
One, two...
Shouta-senpai!
Gosh, they're embarrassing me.
We are extremely pleased to have
a student of our school as the winner
of such an honorable award.
What the hell were you thinking?
I told you to just write whatever,
but you made me win top damn prize.
This is all thanks to constant,
daily efforts finally bearing fruit.
You want to die?
I-I'm sorry.
I hope all of you will take this opportunity
Yet you only landed a participation prize.
to cultivate a habit of reading
in your daily lives.
Shouta-senpai really is cool.
Next we have the award of
excellence for Matsutani Tooru.
Right?
That so? Well, I'll give
him props for being rich.
What's that black stuff?
Huh? Where?
Emerge from darkness,
blacker than darkness.
Purify that which is impure.
Hey, I did it.
Thanks, Mahito.
I can't afford to leave any
residuals of me behind.
What are the veil's effects?
They cannot escape from inside.
Some can enter from outside,
but only those with weak cursed energy.
It's an unannounced veil
in a residential area.
The windows will report it right away.
I hope this plays out as you believe it will.
I think it'll go fine.
The general course was already set
once Junpei landed Sukuna's vessel.
I'll cause the two of them to clash,
and force Itadori Yuuji
into a pact giving Sukuna dominance.
I sure wish Jougo was as level-headed as you.
But it's cute how honest
and straightforward he is.
Anyway, you okay with this?
That finger was a precious resource, right?
It's fine.
The finger from the juvenile center was
quickly absorbed into Itadori Yuuji, after all.
I'd like to have Jujutsu Tech retrieve the one
we placed at Yoshino Junpei's home, as well.
Another ploy?
Yeah.
Well, I'll be taking my leave.
Huh? You're leaving?
You should stay and watch, too.
I'm sure it'll be fun...
watching foolish kids die.
H-Hey! What's wrong with you guys?!
Get a grip! Are you okay?!
They're not dead.
Yoshino?
Why...
Wait, do you know what's going on here?
Sensei.
Make sure you're watching...
You... Those scars...
That's—
...what's already happened,
and what's about to happen.
Yoshino...
I have a question for you.
Are you the one who left that in my home?
What are you—
Wh-What is this?
What did you do?!
That's no good.
Do you still think you're in a position to
answer questions with your own questions?
You are going to die.
Whether your answer is yes or no.
After all, I don't have a technique
to see through your lies,
and you've already done more
than enough to earn it!
So show some sincerity in
your final moments, at least.
I'm... sorry...
And?
Come on!
What are you doing, Junpei?!
Stay out of this, jujutsu sorcerer.
Juju Stroll
The layout was great, but a
three-burner range portends death.
Set it ablaze, Mt. Hiei!
Matsutake for aroma, shimeji for flavor!
The tones of autumn disappear,
together with the tears of the beloved!
Next time on Jujutsu Kaisen, episode 12:
"Bloody Autumn Leaf-viewing."
The hunt is on... for your heart.
Next Episode:
Bloody Autumn Leaf-viewing
Episode 12:
To You, Someday